DOMINIQUE GARRETT

Dallas, TX | 972-900-8414 | dominique.garrett1212@gmail.com

SUMMARY

MBA candidate with 2+ years of experience in small business management. Extensive experience with social media, graphic designing, and digital marketing. Demonstrated a 35% social media growth through successful advertising and promotional campaigns through a direct management of channels. Successfully implemented and introduced innovative social media marketing strategies leading to 30% sales growth.

EXPERIENCE

Lash God | Customer Service Representative | Toronto, ON

12/2020 - Present

- Handle 90+ calls daily, with duties including signing up new customers, retrieving customer data, presenting relevant product information, and cancelling services
- Received an average 85% customer satisfaction rating to date, 15% higher than company average
- Provided basic technical support for clients on a wide range of company products
- Remained courteous and calm, even during moments of customer dissatisfaction
- Tracked every position and every candidates using Microsoft Excel Spreadsheets.

Lash God | Social Media Brand Ambassador | Toronto, ON

06/2019 - 12/2020

- Managed social media channels (Instagram, Twitter, Tik Tok) and increased followers and engagement by 35% across all platforms
- Implemented new systematic method for advertising review process which led to an overall decrease of 30% in internal review time
- Created new marketing campaign for products which drove 15% sales increase year-over-year
- Streamlined market research processes to improve efficiency
- Interfaced with customers and marketing firms to support downstream marketing activities
- Mentored 3 Interns in social media management, campaign creation, and market research

Dolled By Dominique | Owner | Dallas, TX

10/2018 - Present

- Built consistent client base from scratch, achieving annual gross sales of \$100,000. Profit to earnings ratio has been at 35% for the last two years.
- Manage web portal e-Commerce business specializing in beauty and cometic care for women all over.
- Act as liaison between cosmetic distributors and customers
- Promotion via social media platforms to improve brand identity and generate revenue
- Create business plans, arrange financing, review sales, develop marketing strategies, oversee daily activities, and identify business activities
- Sole trademark and LLC holder

Center for the Integration of STEM Education & Research (CISER) | Undergraduate Researcher | Lubbock, TX 06/2017 - 08/2020

- Encourage undergraduate students interested in STEM (Science, Technology, Engineering, Mathematics) to be engaged in an authentic research experience
- Engage in cutting-edge research and build credentials to become future leaders in research, technology, medicine, and teaching.
- Led laboratory bench studies and bioassays for product advancements helping damaged tissue heal through cytokine and growth-factor repositioning.
- Research contributed to leading-edge prototypes, including a biology mesh for hernia repair that is expected to revolutionize the way abdominal wall reconstructive surgery is performed.
- Maintained impeccable standards in time management and leadership during experiments and laboratory deadlines.

SKILLS

Software: Microsoft, Canva, Excel, Google Analytics

Competencies: Decision Making, Communication, Determination

EDUCATION

Texas Tech University, Lubbock, TX Bachelors of Science, Biology, August 2020